{
    "subject": "resource/Adam_Smith_(politician)",
    "predicate": "ontology/party",
    "object": "resource/Democratic_Party_(United_States)",
    "human_readable": "Adam Smith is a member of the Democratic Party (United States).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9555040597915649,
            "question": "Is Adam Smith affiliated with a political party in the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9252747893333435,
            "question": "What political party is Adam Smith a member of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9192301034927368,
            "question": "Does Adam Smith belong to a major American political party?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.868804395198822,
            "question": "Is Adam Smith a member of the Republican Party?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8194805979728699,
            "question": "In American politics, what party does Adam Smith identify with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8141005635261536,
            "question": "What is the name of the political party Adam Smith is associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7231764793395996,
            "question": "What is Adam Smith's political stance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6935214400291443,
            "question": "What is the name of the political party that Adam Smith supports?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6884359121322632,
            "question": "Which political affiliation does Adam Smith hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6262160539627075,
            "question": "To which country's political system does Adam Smith belong?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Adam Smith is a member of the Democratic Party (United States).",
            "html": "dbpedia_4932_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which political affiliation does Adam Smith hold?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4932_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the political party that Adam Smith supports?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4932_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Adam Smith's political stance?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4932_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4932_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4932_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4932_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4932_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4932_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4932_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4932_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4932_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4932_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4932_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Adam Smith is a member of the Democratic Party (United States)\". The context mentions his re-election with 71% of the vote and details about his roles within the Democratic Party, such as being the top Democrat on the House Armed Services Committee since 2011."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}